# **Dylan Wong**

Software Developer, Web Designer, Math & Computer Science Major

(775) 857-7906 dylanwong@nevada.unr.edu wong-innovations.com www.github.com/wong-innovations

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Fox Optimization, Reno NV — QA Intern

DECEMBER 2018 - DECEMBER 2019

Writing code to test the functionality of Fox Optimization's scheduling application. Bug finding, UX enhancing, and functionality verification.

## **Scraps Dog Company**, Sparks NV — Sales Associate

JUNE 2014 - AUGUST 2018

Providing knowledgeable service to caring animal owners, carrying out transactions, and website management for the company.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **School Name**, Location — B.S. in Math & Computer Science

AUGUST 2018 - PRESENT

I am currently a senior pursuing my Bachelors in both Mathematics and Computer Science.

### **PROJECTS**

# **Hackathons** — Competitive Coding

Hackathons are a great test of one's collaboration and coding abilities, as a category winner of the 2018 ACM Hackathon, I am no stranger to the hard work required to complete a project in a tight deadline.

# **GitHub Campus Expert** — Empowering Peers

As a Computer Science student with industry experience, it was undeniable that the university's curriculum does not produce job ready developers. With the GitHub provided training and funding behind me I have embarked to solve this problem through modern workshops and courses for motivated students to bridge this gap in knowledge.

# **App Development** — Portfolio Building

Any free time I manage to find between work, school, and club ultimate frisbee, is spent learning new frameworks and creating the projects featured on my website, such as React a citation generator.

#### **HARD SKILLS**

HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript
SQL and NOSQL Databases
Django and Apollo Server Backends
GraphQL and REST API's
Adobe Suite and MS Office
React and React Native
Graphic Design, UI, UX

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

Communication

Organization

Accountability

Adaptability

**Problem Solving** 

Work Ethic

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a highly motivated individual with a love for learning and problem solving. I have experience in a multitude of programming languages and constantly challenge myself to grow and learn. Both physically and academically, I've never been known to back down from a challenge. I love meeting and working with equally motivated individuals.